[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which story do we meet Grizabella the Glamour Cat?", "correct_answer": "Cats", "incorrect_answers": ["Through the Looking Glass", "The Cats Paw", "The Aristocats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the cartoon Augie Doggie and Doggie Daddy, Doggie Daddy spoke like what entertainer?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Durante", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Chan", "George Burns", "Bill Cosby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a relative of the starfish?", "correct_answer": "Sea Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Sea Urchin", "Sea Cucumber", "Sand Dollar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mixing what colors will result in a brown color?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Red and black", "Black and yellow", "Black and orange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What creature is considered the most venomous on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Box jellyfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Fat-tailed scorpion", "Killer bee", "Cone snail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following animals are herbivorous. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Opossum", "incorrect_answers": ["Guinea pig", "Beaver", "Capybara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When should corn (maize) be planted?", "correct_answer": "Spring", "incorrect_answers": ["Winter", "Fall", "Summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to an interview, George Lucas confided that the name Darth Vader means what?", "correct_answer": "Dark Father", "incorrect_answers": ["Dark Lord", "Evil One", "Dark Leader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of fractions are 4/4, 9/8, and 7/4?", "correct_answer": "Improper fractions", "incorrect_answers": ["Proper fractions", "Similar fractions", "Dissimilar fractions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the city of Bahia Blanca located?", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["Colombia", "Micronesia", "Dominican Republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous movie director worked on the 1985 drama movie The Color Purple, starring Whoopi Goldberg?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Milos Forman", "Tim Burton", "Ingmar Bergman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is true about elephants?", "correct_answer": "The elephant is a good swimmer.", "incorrect_answers": ["The elephant is a good jumper.", "The elephant is not a protected species.", "An elephants skin is 2.5 inches thick."]}]